<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>jnd on Ratheronfire&#39;s Assorted Collection of Odd Projects</title>
    <link>https://ratheronfire.com/categories/jnd/</link>
    <description>Recent content in jnd on Ratheronfire&#39;s Assorted Collection of Odd Projects</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2021 21:59:41 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ratheronfire.com/categories/jnd/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The 100% Accurate Chronological Storyline of Metal Gear (From Memory) [PART 2]</title>
      <link>https://ratheronfire.com/thoughts/jnd/mgs_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2021 21:59:41 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ratheronfire.com/thoughts/jnd/mgs_2/</guid>
      <description>Originally posted to /r/JNDDeskscraps on January 19, 2021.
&amp;hellip;So it&amp;rsquo;s been a while since I did the first part of this, but Metal Gear&amp;rsquo;s been on my mind lately so I want to go back to whatever this dumb project was now. The idea is to recount as much as I can of the games&amp;rsquo; storyline in chronological order, trying to avoid looking anything up if I can. Anyway, after MGS3, there are a couple side games which are questionably canon that I never actually played.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ratheronfire&#39;s Unorganized 1 AM Picard Season 1 Thoughts</title>
      <link>https://ratheronfire.com/thoughts/jnd/picard/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 02:30:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ratheronfire.com/thoughts/jnd/picard/</guid>
      <description>Originally posted to /r/JNDDeskscraps on May 31, 2020.
Since Kirbychu posted his thoughts a while back I wanted to put together some of mine too. It&amp;rsquo;s really late as I&amp;rsquo;m typing this and I&amp;rsquo;m using my phone so things might get a bit messy but oh well.
Characters
Figured I&amp;rsquo;d start off talking about some of the main characters and how I feel about them.
Picard: Even as I&amp;rsquo;m writing this I really don&amp;rsquo;t know how I feel about Picard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 100% Accurate Chronological Storyline of Metal Gear (From Memory) [PART 1]</title>
      <link>https://ratheronfire.com/thoughts/jnd/mgs_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 22:06:49 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ratheronfire.com/thoughts/jnd/mgs_1/</guid>
      <description>Originally posted to /r/JNDDeskscraps on September 1, 2019.
During WWII, a secret alliance between America, China, and I think the Soviet Union amassed a massive cache of funds split across hundreds of shell corporations and dummy accounts. The sequence of transactions necessary to extract all the funds was stored on a chip called the Philosophers&amp;rsquo; Legacy, named after the organization that acquired the fund. One of the Russian members intended to keep the funds for himself and pass them onto his descendants in the hopes they would be used to unite the world and put an end to all the meaningless conflict.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
