<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>reviews on Ratheronfire&#39;s Assorted Collection of Odd Projects</title>
    <link>https://ratheronfire.com/categories/reviews/</link>
    <description>Recent content in reviews on Ratheronfire&#39;s Assorted Collection of Odd Projects</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 00:00:00 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ratheronfire.com/categories/reviews/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Game Reviews</title>
      <link>https://ratheronfire.com/thoughts/reviews/games/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ratheronfire.com/thoughts/reviews/games/</guid>
      <description>Most of the reviews here are copied over from Backloggd, for posterity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Movie Reviews</title>
      <link>https://ratheronfire.com/thoughts/reviews/movies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ratheronfire.com/thoughts/reviews/movies/</guid>
      <description>Most of the reviews here are copied over from Letterboxd, for posterity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Reviews</title>
      <link>https://ratheronfire.com/thoughts/reviews/tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ratheronfire.com/thoughts/reviews/tv/</guid>
      <description>Most of the reviews here are copied over from Serializd, for posterity.
Nothing much to see here right now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Across the Spider-Verse</title>
      <link>https://ratheronfire.com/thoughts/reviews/movies/spiderverse_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ratheronfire.com/thoughts/reviews/movies/spiderverse_2/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ll be honest, I&amp;rsquo;m not really a superhero guy. There&amp;rsquo;s stuff I like, but I tend to only check in on superhero stuff occasionally. Some of the DCAU shows, the Arkham games, that sort of thing. But when it comes to Marvel stuff, my experience is basically only the odd Spiderman thing here and there: I saw the Raimi movies which were outstanding for the most part, the first Amazing Spiderman which was fine I guess, and a bit of that Insomniac game (really need to get back to that, now that it&amp;rsquo;s finally on PC).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sonic Frontiers</title>
      <link>https://ratheronfire.com/thoughts/reviews/games/sonic_frontiers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ratheronfire.com/thoughts/reviews/games/sonic_frontiers/</guid>
      <description>Really didn&amp;rsquo;t expect to enjoy this as much as I did going in, but this game is just so much fun in a way that&amp;rsquo;s kinda hard to describe. Maybe it&amp;rsquo;s because I&amp;rsquo;m used to modern Sonic (or maybe it&amp;rsquo;s because of the mods that I was playing around with) but I didn&amp;rsquo;t have nearly as much trouble with the controls as a lot of other people did. Things like the pop-in and the occasional bug didn&amp;rsquo;t bother me too much, after the first few hours I didn&amp;rsquo;t really pay much attention to them anymore.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Legend of Zelda: Link&#39;s Awakening DX</title>
      <link>https://ratheronfire.com/thoughts/reviews/games/ladx/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ratheronfire.com/thoughts/reviews/games/ladx/</guid>
      <description>Completed the RetroAchievements set for this playthrough. Overall a really solid set, good balance of difficulty without relying on too many easily missable achievements or obnoxious requirements, as well as being a nice excuse to see some of the little touches you might miss otherwise. I did have to start up a second playthrough for the secret seashells achievement though, but that was mainly due to the game locking you out of two of them unless you obtain them at a really specific point.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Star Trek II: The Wrath of Khan</title>
      <link>https://ratheronfire.com/thoughts/reviews/movies/trek_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ratheronfire.com/thoughts/reviews/movies/trek_2/</guid>
      <description>Watched the 40th anniversary theater re-issue with a couple of friends. Still a fantastic movie and one of my all-time favorites, though every time I see it the dumber aspects are more apparent to me.
An entire planet blowing up offscreen and shifting the orbit of another planet The Genesis device being able to create life on a planetary scale from nothing The Genesis device detonating in the middle of a nebula creating a new planet orbiting a star (?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Matrix Revolutions</title>
      <link>https://ratheronfire.com/thoughts/reviews/movies/matrix_3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ratheronfire.com/thoughts/reviews/movies/matrix_3/</guid>
      <description>(Note: I wrote this up as a rough summary of my thoughts after watching the series for the first time leading up to the new movie. Copying them over here for posterity.)
Like with Reloaded, I had absolutely no idea where Revolutions was going to lead me going in. I knew we were going to see Agent Smith in the real world, I knew we were going to see the sentinels attack Zion, and I knew there was going to be something happening with Smith in the Matrix.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Matrix Reloaded</title>
      <link>https://ratheronfire.com/thoughts/reviews/movies/matrix_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ratheronfire.com/thoughts/reviews/movies/matrix_2/</guid>
      <description>(Note: I wrote this up as a rough summary of my thoughts after watching the series for the first time leading up to the new movie. Copying them over here for posterity.)
Look, I&amp;rsquo;ve been on the internet for a while now. I know the Matrix sequels have a&amp;hellip; less than stellar reputation among fans. There are a lot of issues with these movies, and despite everything I&amp;rsquo;ve heard, I wanted to go in with an open mind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Matrix</title>
      <link>https://ratheronfire.com/thoughts/reviews/movies/matrix_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ratheronfire.com/thoughts/reviews/movies/matrix_1/</guid>
      <description>(Note: I wrote this up as a rough summary of my thoughts after watching the series for the first time leading up to the new movie. Copying them over here for posterity.)
Even if you&amp;rsquo;ve never seen The Matrix, you&amp;rsquo;ve seen The Matrix. Very few movies are as iconic and embedded into our culture as this one, and even little things like Switch&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;not like this&amp;rdquo; scene still show up all the time in casual conversation.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
