<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ratheronfire&#39;s Assorted Collection of Odd Projects</title>
    <link>https://ratheronfire.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ratheronfire&#39;s Assorted Collection of Odd Projects</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 00:00:00 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ratheronfire.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Across the Spider-Verse</title>
      <link>https://ratheronfire.com/thoughts/reviews/movies/spiderverse_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ratheronfire.com/thoughts/reviews/movies/spiderverse_2/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ll be honest, I&amp;rsquo;m not really a superhero guy. There&amp;rsquo;s stuff I like, but I tend to only check in on superhero stuff occasionally. Some of the DCAU shows, the Arkham games, that sort of thing. But when it comes to Marvel stuff, my experience is basically only the odd Spiderman thing here and there: I saw the Raimi movies which were outstanding for the most part, the first Amazing Spiderman which was fine I guess, and a bit of that Insomniac game (really need to get back to that, now that it&amp;rsquo;s finally on PC).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stinkoman 20X6 - Version 0.9.0</title>
      <link>https://ratheronfire.com/projects/stinkoman/0.9.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ratheronfire.com/projects/stinkoman/0.9.0/</guid>
      <description> Play in the browser Windows Mac Linux Android Patch Notes Added Level 9 Added NES/Game Boy/GBC Palettes (Very early concepts currently) Minor collision and movement fixes </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sonic Frontiers</title>
      <link>https://ratheronfire.com/thoughts/reviews/games/sonic_frontiers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ratheronfire.com/thoughts/reviews/games/sonic_frontiers/</guid>
      <description>Really didn&amp;rsquo;t expect to enjoy this as much as I did going in, but this game is just so much fun in a way that&amp;rsquo;s kinda hard to describe. Maybe it&amp;rsquo;s because I&amp;rsquo;m used to modern Sonic (or maybe it&amp;rsquo;s because of the mods that I was playing around with) but I didn&amp;rsquo;t have nearly as much trouble with the controls as a lot of other people did. Things like the pop-in and the occasional bug didn&amp;rsquo;t bother me too much, after the first few hours I didn&amp;rsquo;t really pay much attention to them anymore.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Legend of Zelda: Link&#39;s Awakening DX</title>
      <link>https://ratheronfire.com/thoughts/reviews/games/ladx/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ratheronfire.com/thoughts/reviews/games/ladx/</guid>
      <description>Completed the RetroAchievements set for this playthrough. Overall a really solid set, good balance of difficulty without relying on too many easily missable achievements or obnoxious requirements, as well as being a nice excuse to see some of the little touches you might miss otherwise. I did have to start up a second playthrough for the secret seashells achievement though, but that was mainly due to the game locking you out of two of them unless you obtain them at a really specific point.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stinkoman 20X6 - Version 0.8.0</title>
      <link>https://ratheronfire.com/projects/stinkoman/0.8.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ratheronfire.com/projects/stinkoman/0.8.0/</guid>
      <description> Play in the browser Windows Mac Linux Android Patch Notes Added Level 8 Added support for alternate sprite palettes </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Star Trek II: The Wrath of Khan</title>
      <link>https://ratheronfire.com/thoughts/reviews/movies/trek_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ratheronfire.com/thoughts/reviews/movies/trek_2/</guid>
      <description>Watched the 40th anniversary theater re-issue with a couple of friends. Still a fantastic movie and one of my all-time favorites, though every time I see it the dumber aspects are more apparent to me.
An entire planet blowing up offscreen and shifting the orbit of another planet The Genesis device being able to create life on a planetary scale from nothing The Genesis device detonating in the middle of a nebula creating a new planet orbiting a star (?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stinkoman 20X6 - Version 0.7.0</title>
      <link>https://ratheronfire.com/projects/stinkoman/0.7.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ratheronfire.com/projects/stinkoman/0.7.0/</guid>
      <description> Play in the browser Windows Mac Linux Android Patch Notes Added Level 7 Some improvements to collision boxes Re-timed player animations for greater accuracy Added integer scale and aspect ratio settings Added touch controls toggle Improvements for controller input on menus Improved ladder controls Cleaned up death animations </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stinkoman 20X6 - Version 0.6.0</title>
      <link>https://ratheronfire.com/projects/stinkoman/0.6.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ratheronfire.com/projects/stinkoman/0.6.0/</guid>
      <description> Play in the browser Windows Mac Linux Android Patch Notes Added Level 6 Added more context menu functionality to level editor Improved camera behavior in level editor Changed sprites for 2-Up </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Matrix Revolutions</title>
      <link>https://ratheronfire.com/thoughts/reviews/movies/matrix_3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ratheronfire.com/thoughts/reviews/movies/matrix_3/</guid>
      <description>(Note: I wrote this up as a rough summary of my thoughts after watching the series for the first time leading up to the new movie. Copying them over here for posterity.)
Like with Reloaded, I had absolutely no idea where Revolutions was going to lead me going in. I knew we were going to see Agent Smith in the real world, I knew we were going to see the sentinels attack Zion, and I knew there was going to be something happening with Smith in the Matrix.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Matrix Reloaded</title>
      <link>https://ratheronfire.com/thoughts/reviews/movies/matrix_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ratheronfire.com/thoughts/reviews/movies/matrix_2/</guid>
      <description>(Note: I wrote this up as a rough summary of my thoughts after watching the series for the first time leading up to the new movie. Copying them over here for posterity.)
Look, I&amp;rsquo;ve been on the internet for a while now. I know the Matrix sequels have a&amp;hellip; less than stellar reputation among fans. There are a lot of issues with these movies, and despite everything I&amp;rsquo;ve heard, I wanted to go in with an open mind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Matrix</title>
      <link>https://ratheronfire.com/thoughts/reviews/movies/matrix_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ratheronfire.com/thoughts/reviews/movies/matrix_1/</guid>
      <description>(Note: I wrote this up as a rough summary of my thoughts after watching the series for the first time leading up to the new movie. Copying them over here for posterity.)
Even if you&amp;rsquo;ve never seen The Matrix, you&amp;rsquo;ve seen The Matrix. Very few movies are as iconic and embedded into our culture as this one, and even little things like Switch&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;not like this&amp;rdquo; scene still show up all the time in casual conversation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stinkoman 20X6 - Version 0.5.0</title>
      <link>https://ratheronfire.com/projects/stinkoman/0.5.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ratheronfire.com/projects/stinkoman/0.5.0/</guid>
      <description> Play in the browser Windows Mac Linux Android Patch Notes Added Level 5 Added proof-of-concept level editor Various balances/tweaks Added fall velocity cap Better ladder behavior Collision detection improvements Improved camera usability Several enemy bugfixes </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stinkoman 20X6 - Version 0.4.1</title>
      <link>https://ratheronfire.com/projects/stinkoman/0.4.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2021 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ratheronfire.com/projects/stinkoman/0.4.1/</guid>
      <description> Play in the browser Windows Mac Linux Android Patch Notes Fixed extra lives not reflecting on UI after collecting Fixed issues with cutscene viewer. Fixed Stlunko&amp;rsquo;s conveyor belt not stopping on death. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stinkoman 20X6 - Version 0.4.0</title>
      <link>https://ratheronfire.com/projects/stinkoman/0.4.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2021 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ratheronfire.com/projects/stinkoman/0.4.0/</guid>
      <description> Play in the browser Windows Mac Linux Android Patch Notes Added Levels 4.1-4.3 Added options screen to pause menu Added Boss Rush mode &amp;amp; level select Added persistent time trial records Added bug reporting interface Level progress is now saved between sessions Added extra font options Various UI improvements Fixed issue with bottomless pit recovery placing the player in a death loop A whole host of other minor fixes/tweaks </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stinkoman 20X6 - Version 0.3.0</title>
      <link>https://ratheronfire.com/projects/stinkoman/0.3.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ratheronfire.com/projects/stinkoman/0.3.0/</guid>
      <description> Play in the browser Windows Mac Linux Android Patch Notes Added levels 2.1-3.3 Reduced build size Added time attack mode with Stinkoman and 1-Up playable Replaced inaccurate sound effects Made Stinkoman&amp;rsquo;s attack more accurate to the original Added a couple easter eggs Improved controller support Various bugflxes/accuracy improvements </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stinkoman 20X6 - Version 0.2.1</title>
      <link>https://ratheronfire.com/projects/stinkoman/0.2.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ratheronfire.com/projects/stinkoman/0.2.1/</guid>
      <description> Play in the browser Windows Mac Linux Android Patch Notes Fixed hidden portion of drills sometimes rendering Fixed tiling issues in 1.1 Fixed level display being cut off Fixed post-boss battle behavior Improved background appearance Added the hidden power crunch in 1.1 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stinkoman 20X6 - Version 0.2.0</title>
      <link>https://ratheronfire.com/projects/stinkoman/0.2.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ratheronfire.com/projects/stinkoman/0.2.0/</guid>
      <description> Play in the browser Windows Mac Linux Android Patch Notes Added Level 1.2, 1.3 Added title menu, intro screens, and cutscenes Added rebindable controls &amp;amp; audio settings Implemented death, lives, checkpoints, end-of-level flags Generally more accurate to the original Various Bugfixes </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stinkoman 20X6 - Version 0.1.0</title>
      <link>https://ratheronfire.com/projects/stinkoman/0.1.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ratheronfire.com/projects/stinkoman/0.1.0/</guid>
      <description> Play in the browser Windows Mac Linux Android Patch Notes Initial release Added level 1.1 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hades Run Suggester</title>
      <link>https://ratheronfire.com/projects/hades-suggester/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2021 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ratheronfire.com/projects/hades-suggester/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 100% Accurate Chronological Storyline of Metal Gear (From Memory) [PART 2]</title>
      <link>https://ratheronfire.com/thoughts/jnd/mgs_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2021 21:59:41 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ratheronfire.com/thoughts/jnd/mgs_2/</guid>
      <description>Originally posted to /r/JNDDeskscraps on January 19, 2021.
&amp;hellip;So it&amp;rsquo;s been a while since I did the first part of this, but Metal Gear&amp;rsquo;s been on my mind lately so I want to go back to whatever this dumb project was now. The idea is to recount as much as I can of the games&amp;rsquo; storyline in chronological order, trying to avoid looking anything up if I can. Anyway, after MGS3, there are a couple side games which are questionably canon that I never actually played.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ratheronfire&#39;s Unorganized 1 AM Picard Season 1 Thoughts</title>
      <link>https://ratheronfire.com/thoughts/jnd/picard/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 02:30:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ratheronfire.com/thoughts/jnd/picard/</guid>
      <description>Originally posted to /r/JNDDeskscraps on May 31, 2020.
Since Kirbychu posted his thoughts a while back I wanted to put together some of mine too. It&amp;rsquo;s really late as I&amp;rsquo;m typing this and I&amp;rsquo;m using my phone so things might get a bit messy but oh well.
Characters
Figured I&amp;rsquo;d start off talking about some of the main characters and how I feel about them.
Picard: Even as I&amp;rsquo;m writing this I really don&amp;rsquo;t know how I feel about Picard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 100% Accurate Chronological Storyline of Metal Gear (From Memory) [PART 1]</title>
      <link>https://ratheronfire.com/thoughts/jnd/mgs_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 22:06:49 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ratheronfire.com/thoughts/jnd/mgs_1/</guid>
      <description>Originally posted to /r/JNDDeskscraps on September 1, 2019.
During WWII, a secret alliance between America, China, and I think the Soviet Union amassed a massive cache of funds split across hundreds of shell corporations and dummy accounts. The sequence of transactions necessary to extract all the funds was stored on a chip called the Philosophers&amp;rsquo; Legacy, named after the organization that acquired the fund. One of the Russian members intended to keep the funds for himself and pass them onto his descendants in the hopes they would be used to unite the world and put an end to all the meaningless conflict.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>/r/JNDDeskscraps Archive</title>
      <link>https://ratheronfire.com/categories/jnd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ratheronfire.com/categories/jnd/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://ratheronfire.com/categories/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ratheronfire.com/categories/projects/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reviews</title>
      <link>https://ratheronfire.com/categories/reviews/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ratheronfire.com/categories/reviews/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
